SPORTS FESTIVAL
THE DAY OF THE SPORTS FESTIVAL 6:30 AM
Perception
THE DAY OF THE SPORTS FESTIVAL 7:00 AM
FINAL MORNING PRACTICE
8:00 AM GIRLS' HAIR SETTING
THE SHORT-HAIRED CREW WITH NOTHING TO DO
8:20 AM
20 MINUTES EARLIER
FRIENDLY SENIORS WHO THEY'VE
NEVER REALLY TALKED TO BEFORE
SNAP
SPORTS FESTIVAL
MORNING SEGMENT
OBSTACLE RACE
GIRLS' POLE PULL
ALL-STUDENT RELAY RACE
(1ST YEAR)
DASH
PLOP PLOP
CLUB COMPETITION RELAY RACE
CHITTER-CHATTER
WARM AND PLEASANT
WHOOSH
THUD
GOTCHA!
LIFT
WHOOSH
PANTING
AFTERNOON CHEER BATTLE SEGMENT
EACH TEAM FINISHED WITHOUT A HITCH
PHOTO-TAKING TIME
(THE POINTS ARE BEING TALLIED)
FIRST-YEAR STUDENTS
CHITTER-CHATTER A-HA-HA
THUMP
BOUNCE BOUNCE
I'M BEING BECKONED...
WALKING
SWIFT
CLICK
SCURRY
HALF-CLOSED EYES & HALF-OPEN MOUTH
THUMP THUMP
IT'D BE OUT OF CHARACTER
WOULD IT BE CREEPY?
I'M NOT GREAT WITH PHOTOS
IN THE FIRST PLACE
WILL MY FEELINGS BE EXPOSED?
IT MIGHT SEEM UNNATURAL
WILL SHE BE SCARED OF ME?
FLUSTER
BONK
FWUMP
GRIN
WAIT, IT WAS YOUR BIRTHDAY?!
YOU SHOULD'VE TOLD US.
IS IT SOMETHING PEOPLE
USUALLY TELL OTHERS?
GLANCE
LOOKS AROUND
DOING IT
HAHA
FOUND YOU!
GLANCE, GLANCE
KNOCK
FWUMP
HAHA
HEE-HEE-HEE...
HEY, COME ON...
WHAT?
GAPING
THUD
CLICK
GRADE 2 CLASS 2
AFTER HOMEROOM
NOISY
LAST YEAR'S SPORTS FESTIVAL...
A CLASS WITH ZERO UNITY
GRADE 2 CLASS 2 SPORTS COMMITTEE
HEEHEE...
HE'S HERE FOR SOME REASON
SIT
BLUE SQUAD
ROGER THAT OK
ENDLESS RESPONSES
CREAK
UH, UM...
GLANCE, GLANCE
NOD
SATURDAY...
SUPPLIES BORROWING RACE
SUPPLY ROOM
UPPI
SWIFT
CLICK-CLICK-CLICK-CLICK-CLICK
SWIFT MOVEMENTS